

CONTACT

33 25 48 07 67



Guadalajara, Jalisco

https://luisenriquesolis.com/ luisenrique.solisnavarro@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I am a creative person, with ability for interpersonal relationships. I am proactive and fast learning, I have a great facility for understanding abstract, logical or ethereal concepts. Passionate about technology, motivated to learn and improve. I have experience supervising, motivating and managing small work teams (from 2 to 5 people).

SKILLS



Javascript / ES6+



Node.js / Express / API



Ruby / Ruby on Rails



React js / SSR React



HTML5 / CSS / SASS



ORM / SQL / MongoDb

Luis Enrique Solis Navarro

Full Stack Js / RoR Developer

Visit my portafolio at: https://luisenriquesolis.com/

WORK EXPERIENCE

ZION GDL

Co-founder

April 2011 - Dec 2019

- Technical support, creation and design of marketing campaigns (images and videos), administration of sales, purchasing and customer service personnel.
- Communication and contact with suppliers from China for the importation of products.

CFE (Comisión Federal de Electricidad)

On-site technical support engineer

Jan 2010 - Feb 2011

 Creation and maintenance of the quality index tracking system for the Jalisco Transmission Zone (Ruby on Rails / Active Record / Postgre).
Preventive and corrective maintenance to computer systems, networks and related technologies. Attention to users directly on site.
Management of 1 technical support partner who helped with the tasks.

Global Vantage Design Source

Embedded systems tester

Oct 2007 - Oct 2008

 Implementation and validation of embedded systems for the Honeywell company; present in the FMS (Flight Management System) of the Agusta model AW139 / AW109 helicopters.

Education

Pluralsight

Full stack Js Bootcamp.

December 2019 - Nowadays

Universidad de Guadalajara

Computer science degree.

August 2003 - June 2007

English level: B2.

Now learning: React Native / GraphQL.

Other skills.

English Level B2, MVC architecture, Webpack, Babel, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premier, Git, Github, Visual Studio Code, Customer support, Sales, Marketing.

Hobbies.

Technology (Hardware), Cycling, Swimming, Yoga, Philosophy, Oriental Cultures.

LET ME HELP YOU TO CREATE

CONTACT



33 25 48 07 67 | luisenrique.solisnavarro@gmail.com | https://luisenriquesolis.com/



